AIDIL FITRAH ROMADHONI

Tulungagung - Rejotangan - Pakisrejo, 66293· +6289683322400 doni.smpn1gmail.com · linkedin: aidil-fitrah-romadhoni

I am a student who has been learning to become a programmer for the past two years. I have been studying UI/UX design, Web Development, as well as improving my communication skills to be able to effectively manage teams.

EXPERIENCE

2023/10 – 2024/02 BACKEND DEV, HALTECH

- I am currently studying GoLang, which will be utilized as an API to connect to a Postgres database, ultimately consumed by a Flutter frontend.
- I also understand the concept of a database and API usage

2024/02 - NOW

FULLSTACK WEB DEV, HALTECH

• Creating a website using Firebase that will be able to output real-time data, including IoT data that provides real-time updates on the website.

EDUCATION

2019/07 – 2022/06 JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL, SMP Negeri 1 Rejotangan

General education

2022/07 – NOW

SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL, SMK Negeri 1 Boyolangu

Language, Organization, and Programming

SKILLS

GENERAL

- Web Dev
- UI/UX
- Video Editing
- Design
- 3D Modeling
- Speaking

• LANGUAGE

- English
- Indonesia

• TECHNICAL

- HTML,CSS,JS,PHP.
- Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Corel.
- Capcut
- Sketchup, Blender